Curriculum Vitae

Tomasz Maksim

5 Chestnut Grove Kilcock Co.Kildare

phone: 083 309 3550

e-mail: tomaszmaksim@gmail.com



About me:

I'm experienced in retail, in a field of marketing and project management. I have good interpersonal and organisational skills. I'm reliable, flexible and creative with initialive to defining new goals.

While I keep busy learning new web technologies I use my problem solving skills and attention to detail.

Key Skills:

JAVA 8, HTML 5, CSS, MySQL, Bootstrap, Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop, Figma, Microsoft Office, Google Maps API, Gant Project Management, Balsamic Mockups.

Languages: Fluent English and Polish, basic German.

Additional training:

Full cat. B driving license, Manual Handling, CompTIA Cloud Essentials, Google Analytics, HACCP, Payback - payroll software

Education:

09.2020 - present	JavaScript and React online course
2020 - 08.2020	Programming using HTML & CSS online course
2019 - 05.2019	Adobe Certified Associate online course
2017 - 05.2018	JAVA 8 Software Developer Course, Cenit College Naas
2016 - 12.2016	Multi Digital Skills Course, Cenit College Naas
1999 - 2001	Management and Marketing College in Wroclaw, Poland
1999	Secondary School Leaving examination

Work experience:

Dec 2018 – present Self-employed, props for events rental and web design

Responsibilities:

Daily customer service,

design and implementation of photo templates for the Magic Mirror photo-booth, social media advertisement,

invoicing,

deliveries and collections of the rented equipment, maintenance and troubleshooting, design and creation of the websites, logo design from the scratch.

Sep 2010 - Dec 2016

Self-employed, Hussar Polish Groceries

Responsibilities:

Daily customer service,
coordination of the shipments,
stock control,
goods delivery,
oversee of accounts, payroll and rosters,
design and execution of marketing campaigns,
training of staff,
on-site refrigeration devices maintenance and troubleshooting.

Dec 2007 – March 2010 Hewlett-Packard Leixlip, Co.Kildare

Role: Assembly line operator

Responsibilities:

Monitoring work of printer cartridges assembly line, maintainance of stock levels of materials, work in four cycle shift pattern, performance of regular checks and diagnostics on the line, responsible for quality of products according to company GMP's, assistance to engineers during tests and experiments, small technical issues troubleshooting.

Jan 2007 – Dec 2007 IBM Damastown, Dublin

Role: Warehouse employee

Responsibilities:

Picking and packing orders, check for missing or damaged items, random inspections of ready orders.

Mar 2006- Dec 2006 St. Jameses Hospital Dublin

Role: Security Officer

Responsibilities:

Providing security for patients and staff on the hospital grounds and A&E.

2001 – 2005 Maxima Ladies clothes retail shop

Role: Sales Assistant

Responsibilities:

Providing excellent customer experience, cashier responsibilities, deliveries management.

Interests:

Books, movies and sports.

References:

Delighted to supply upon request.

Portfolio:

https://loving-keller-c8b295.netlify.app/

